{
    "challenges": [
        {
            "type": "explain-me",
            "question": "pip install --upgrade robotframework-seleniumlibrary",
            "src": "https://github.com/robotframework/SeleniumLibrary",
            "answer": "Install Python-specific modules and use --upgrade to upgrade the existing python specific module"
        },
        {
            "type": "explain-me",
            "question": "sudo pip install -r requirements.txt",
            "src": "https://github.com/qxf2/qxf2-page-object-model",
            "answer": "Install pre-requisite libraries/dependencies"
        },
        {
            "type": "explain-me",
            "question": "git submodule sync",
            "src": "https://git-scm.com/book/en/v2/Git-Tools-Submodules",
            "answer": "Apply the remote repo's configuration to your local submodule repos. Make the child repo follow the parent repo. It is similar to master/slave"
        },
        {
            "type": "explain-me",
            "question": "source path to python exe location/scripts/activate",
            "src": "https://gist.github.com/simonw/4835a22c79a8d3c29dd155c716b19e16",
            "answer": "Activating python virtualenv"
        },
        {
            "type": "explain-me",
            "question": "sudo apt-get update && sudo apt-get upgrade && sudo apt-get install",
            "src": "https://github.com/M4cs/BabySploit",
            "answer": "These are the common commands in Linux to install and upgrade packages."
        },
        {
            "type": "explain-me",
            "question": "python -m http.server {port}",
            "src": "https://github.com/IBM/ibm.github.io",
            "answer": "To run the tests on the desired port or to test changes locally."
        },
        {
            "type": "explain-me",
            "question": "docker-compose up --build",
            "src": "https://github.com/PokeAPI/pokeapi",
            "answer": "To start the process in detached mode and specify the -d switch to start in detached mode."
        },
        {
            "type": "explain-me",
            "question": "curl -L https://git.io/rustlings | bash",
            "src": "https://github.com/rust-lang/rustlings",
            "answer": "To install the package to the default path"
        },
        {
            "type": "explain-me",
            "question": "xvfb-run --server-args='-screen 0 1024x768x24' python test_script.py",
            "src": "https://github.com/joyzoursky/docker-python-chromedriver",
            "answer": "To run the script in a headless display screen with the given dimensions."
        },
        {
            "type": "explain-me",
            "question": "ssh -i /Users/yaroslav/.ncluster/ncluster5-yaroslav-316880547378-us-east-1.pem -o StrictHostKeyChecking=no ubuntu@18.206.193.26tmux a",
            "src": "https://github.com/joyzoursky/docker-python-chromedriver",
            "answer": "Ssh/Login into a Ubuntu instance using a .pem file(trust chain with user identification) where host key is not being checked for login purposes."
        }
    ]
}